Beware of Mr. Baker is a documentary, music film directed by Jay Bulger.
Ginger Baker is known for playing in Cream and Blind Faith, but the world's greatest drummer didn’t hit
his stride until 1972, when he arrived in Nigeria and discovered Fela Kuti's Afrobeat.
After leaving Nigeria, Ginger returned to his pattern of drug-induced self-destruction, and countless groundbreaking musical
works, eventually settling in South Africa, where the 73-year-old lives with his young bride and 39 polo ponies.
This documentary includes interviews with Eric Clapton,
Steve Winwood, Carlos Santana and more.
Beware of Mr.
With every smash of the drum is a man smashing his way through life.
Self, played by Ginger Baker.
Self, played by Jay Bulger.
Self, played by Eric Clapton.
Self, played by Jack Bruce.
Self, played by Tony Allen.
Self, played by Bob Adcock.
Beware of Mr.
Baker is a 2012 American documentary film by Jay Bulger
about the jazz and rock drummer Ginger Baker.